PERSONAL INFO

() 054-804-7997

<u>avrikaufman@gmail.com</u>

https://avikaufman.tech/

www.linkedin.com/in/avikaufman-b93540200

https://github.com/avikaufman

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

Java

Python

C #

SQL

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Git VCS

Bash

PERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork

Full Dedication

Pursuing Excellence

Not afraid of hard work

Proactive

Autodidact

HOBBIES

Chess

Hiking

Slackline

Avi Kaufman

A B.Sc. Student, Looking for a Student Position

I departed the Ultra-Orthodox community, independently pursued my education, earned a full "Bagrut" in two years excelling in English and math, and found my passion for math and programming.

Today, I am in the last year of my B.A. in Computer Science at Reichman University, supported by the "Keren Or" scholarship.

Highly motivated, enthusiastic, looking for new opportunities.

EDUCATION

Present - Last year (4th Year) of a B.A. in Computer Science at Reichman University, Herzliya.

SELECTED COURSES:

Data Structures, Algorithms, Operating Systems, Advanced Programming, Machine Learning From Data, Full Stack Development

PROJECT:

Blog application with React front-end, Python REST API back-end, MySQL database, deployed on AWS (RDS & EC2)

EXTRACURRICULAR:

Pulse Healthtech Innovation Entrepreneurship Club Volunteer Tutor for "Keren Or" scholarship, Math and Programing

2017 - External Bagroot (High School Equivalency test), Tel-Aviv

2010 - Knesset Meir Yeshiva, Rishon Le'Zion

COURSES

2022 - Intro to machine learning, Kaggle

2019 - Computer Science and Python Programing, Campus

2016 - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT) Course, MDA

EMPLOYMENT

2018 - Present - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT), IDF Disabled Veterans Organization "Beit Halochem" Tel Aviv

VOLUNTEERING

2018 - Present - "Hillel" and "Out for Change" nonprofits

NATIONAL SERVICE

2016 - 2017 - Emergency Medical Technician (EMT), Magen David Adom (MDA), Tel Aviv

2015 - 2016 - Group Leader, <u>Jordan River Village</u> camp for children living with chronic diseases, Givat Avni

2013 - 2014 - Pre-Military "Mechinat HaEmek" program